<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
	<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
		<MASTER_PAD_VERSION>1.15</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
		<MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to dissemminate information to anyone interested in their software products.  To find out more go to http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
	</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
	<Company_Info>
		<Company_Name>pgAdmin Team</Company_Name>
		<Address_1/>
		<Address_2/>
		<City_Town/>
		<State_Province/>
		<Zip_Postal_Code/>
		<Country/>
		<Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.pgadmin.org</Company_WebSite_URL>
		<Contact_Info>
			<Author_First_Name/>
			<Author_Last_Name/>
			<Author_Email/>
			<Contact_First_Name>pgAdmin</Contact_First_Name>
			<Contact_Last_Name>Team</Contact_Last_Name>
			<Contact_Email>pad@pgadmin.org</Contact_Email>
		</Contact_Info>
		<Support_Info>
			<Sales_Email/>
			<Support_Email>pgadmin-support@postgresql.org</Support_Email>
			<General_Email/>
			<Sales_Phone/>
			<Support_Phone/>
			<General_Phone/>
			<Fax_Phone/>
		</Support_Info>
	</Company_Info>
	<Program_Info>
		<Program_Name>pgAdmin III for PostgreSQL</Program_Name>
		<Program_Version>1.02</Program_Version>
		<Program_Release_Month>01</Program_Release_Month>
		<Program_Release_Day>27</Program_Release_Day>
		<Program_Release_Year>2004</Program_Release_Year>
		<Program_Cost_Dollars>0</Program_Cost_Dollars>
		<Program_Cost_Other_Code/>
		<Program_Cost_Other/>
		<Program_Type>Freeware</Program_Type>
		<Program_Release_Status>New Release</Program_Release_Status>
		<Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
		<Program_OS_Support>WinXP,WinNT4.x,Windows2000,Unix,Linux</Program_OS_Support>
		<Program_Language>Afrikaans,Arabic,Chinese,Czech,Danish,English,French,German,Greek,Hungarian,Italian,Japanese,Polish,Portuguese,Russian,Spanish,Swedish,Taiwanese,Turkish</Program_Language>
		<Program_Change_Info/>
		<Program_System_Requirements>PostgreSQL 7.3/7.4</Program_System_Requirements>
		<Program_Specific_Category>Development Tools</Program_Specific_Category>
		<Program_Categories>Database::Management,Database::Utilities</Program_Categories>
		<File_Info>
			<Filename_Versioned>pgadmin3.zip</Filename_Versioned>
			<Filename_Previous>pgadmin3.zip</Filename_Previous>
			<Filename_Generic>pgadmin3.zip</Filename_Generic>
			<Filename_Long>pgadmin3.zip</Filename_Long>
			<File_Size_Bytes/>
			<File_Size_K>4821</File_Size_K>
			<File_Size_MB>4.7</File_Size_MB>
		</File_Info>
		<Expire_Info>
			<Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
			<Expire_Count/>
			<Expire_Based_On/>
			<Expire_Other_Info/>
			<Expire_Month/>
			<Expire_Day/>
			<Expire_Year/>
		</Expire_Info>
		<Includes_VB_Runtime>N</Includes_VB_Runtime>
		<Includes_JAVA_VM>N</Includes_JAVA_VM>
		<Includes_DirectX>N</Includes_DirectX>
	</Program_Info>
	<Program_Descriptions>
		<English>
			<Keywords>pgadmin,pgadmin2,pgdmin3,PostgreSQL,postgresql,postgres,sql,database,development,gui,administration,tool,software,free,pg,pg-admin</Keywords>
			<Char_Desc_45>Administration Centre for PostgreSQL</Char_Desc_45>
			<Char_Desc_80>Administration Centre for the PostgreSQL database, freeware</Char_Desc_80>
			<Char_Desc_250>Administration Centre for the PostgreSQL database, freeware. Includes a graphical administration interface, an SQL query tool, a procedural code editor and much more. Designed to answer the needs of most users.</Char_Desc_250>
			<Char_Desc_450>Administration Centre for the PostgreSQL database, freeware. Includes a graphical administration interface, an SQL query tool, a procedural code editor and much more. pgAdmin III is designed to answer the needs of most users, from writing simple SQL queries to developing complex databases. Available in more than 30 languages and for several operating systems.</Char_Desc_450>
			<Char_Desc_2000>Administration Centre for the PostgreSQL database, freeware. Includes a graphical administration interface, an SQL query tool, a procedural code editor and much more. pgAdmin III is designed to answer the needs of most users, from writing simple SQL queries to developing complex databases. The graphical interface supports all PostgreSQL features and makes administration easy. Available in more than 30 languages and for several operating systems, including MS Windows, GNU/Linux and FreeBSD.</Char_Desc_2000>
		</English>

		<Afrikaans>
			<Keywords>pgadmin,pgadmin2,pgdmin3,PostgreSQL,postgresql,postgres,sql,database,development,gui,administration,tool,software,free,pg,pg-admin</Keywords>
			<Char_Desc_45>Administrasie van PostgreSQL-databasisse</Char_Desc_45>
			<Char_Desc_80>Gratis administrasiesentrum vir PostgreSQL-databasisse met grafiese koppelvlak</Char_Desc_80>
			<Char_Desc_250>Gratis administrasiesentrum vir PostgreSQL-databasisse. Dit bevat 'n grafiese koppelvlak, 'n SQL-navraaghulpmiddel, 'n prosedure-redigeerder en vele meer - ontwerp vir die meeste gebruikers se behoeftes.</Char_Desc_250>
			<Char_Desc_450>Gratis administrasiesentrum vir PostgreSQL-databasisse. Dit bevat 'n grafiese koppelvlak, 'n SQL-navraaghulpmiddel, 'n prosedure-redigeerder en vele meer. pgAdmin III is ontwerp vir die meeste gebruikers se behoeftes, van eenvoudige SQL-navrae tot die ontwikkeling van komplekse databasisse. Dit is beskikbaar in meer as 30 tale en vir verskeie bedryfstelsels.</Char_Desc_450>
			<Char_Desc_2000>Gratis administrasiesentrum vir PostgreSQL-databasisse. Dit bevat 'n grafiese administrasiekoppelvlak, 'n SQL-navraaghulpmiddel, 'n redigeerder vir programkode van prosedures en vele meer. pgAdmin III is ontwerp om vir die behoeftes van die meeste gebruikers voorsiening te maak, van die skryf van eenvoudige SQL-navrae tot die ontwikkeling van komplekse databasisse. Die grafiese koppelvlak ondersteun alle PostgreSQL-funksionaliteit en dit maak administrasie maklik. Dit is beskikbaar in meer as 30 tale en vir verskeie bedryfstelsels, insluitende MS Windows, GNU/Linux en FreeBSD.</Char_Desc_2000>
		</Afrikaans>

		<French>
			<Keywords>pgadmin,pgadmin2,pgdmin3,PostgreSQL,postgresql,postgres,sql,database,development,gui,administration,tool,software,free,pg,pg-admin</Keywords>
			<Char_Desc_45>Logiciel d'administration de PostgreSQL</Char_Desc_45>
			<Char_Desc_80>Logiciel libre d'admistration de la base de données PostgreSQL</Char_Desc_80>
			<Char_Desc_250>Logiciel libre d'administration de PostgreSQL. Comprend une interface graphique d'administration, un outil de requêtes SQL, un éditeur de code procédural et bien plus encore. Conçu pour répondre à la plupart des besoins.</Char_Desc_250>
			<Char_Desc_450>Logiciel libre d'administration de la base de données PostgreSQL. Comprend une interface graphique d'administration, un outil de requêtes SQL, un éditeur de code procédural et bien plus encore. pgAdmin III est conçu pour répondre à la plupart des besoins, depuis l'écriture de simples requêtes SQL jusqu'au développement de bases de données complexes. Disponible dans plus de 30 langues et pour plusieurs systèmes d'exploitation.</Char_Desc_450>
			<Char_Desc_2000>Logiciel libre d'administration de la base de données PostgreSQL. Comprend une interface graphique d'administration, un outil de requêtes SQL, un éditeur de code procédural et bien plus encore. pgAdmin III est conçu pour répondre à la plupart des besoins, depuis l'écriture de simples requêtes SQL jusqu'au développement de bases de données complexes. L'interface graphique supporte les fonctionnalités de PostgreSQL les plus récentes et fait de l'administration un jeu d'enfant. Disponible dans plus de 30 langues et pour plusieurs systèmes d'exploitation, y compris MS Windows, GNU/Linux et FreeBSD.</Char_Desc_2000>
		</French>

		<German>
			<Keywords>pgadmin,pgadmin2,pgdmin3,PostgreSQL,postgresql,postgres,sql,database,development,gui,administration,tool,software,free,pg,pg-admin</Keywords>
			<Char_Desc_45>Administrationszentrum für PostgreSQL</Char_Desc_45>
			<Char_Desc_80>Grafische Administrationsoberfläche für das PostgreSQL Datenbanksystem</Char_Desc_80>
			<Char_Desc_250>Freies Administrationstool für das PostgreSQL Datenbanksystem. Enthält eine grafische Admistrationsoberfläche, ein SQL Query Tool, ein Editor für prozeduralen Code und etliches mehr. pgAdmin III dürfte praktisch allen Ansprüchen an ein Datenbanktool gerecht werden.</Char_Desc_250>
			<Char_Desc_450>Freies Administrationstool für das PostgreSQL Datenbanksystem. Enthält eine grafische Admistrationsoberfläche, ein SQL Query Tool, ein Editor für prozeduralen Code und etliches mehr. pgAdmin III wurde entwickelt um den Anforderungen einer breiten Schicht von Benutzern, vom Schreiben einfacher Queries bis zur Entwicklung komplexer Datenbanken, zu entsprechen. Das Programm ist in mehr als 30 Sprachen übersetzt und steht für diverse Betriebssysteme einschließlich Windows, Linux und FreeBSD zur Verfügung.</Char_Desc_450>
			<Char_Desc_2000>Freies Administrationstool für das PostgreSQL Datenbanksystem. Enthält eine grafische Admistrationsoberfläche, ein SQL Query Tool, ein Editor für prozeduralen Code und etliches mehr. pgAdmin III wurde entwickelt um den Anforderungen einer breiten Schicht von Benutzern, vom Schreiben einfacher Queries bis zur Entwicklung komplexer Datenbanken, zu entsprechen. Die grafische Oberfläche unterstützt sämtliche PostgreSQL Features und macht die Administration sehr einfach. Das Programm ist in mehr als 30 Sprachen übersetzt und steht für diverse Betriebssysteme einschließlich Windows, Linux und FreeBSD zur Verfügung.</Char_Desc_2000>
		</German>

		<Japanese>
			<Keywords>pgadmin,pgadmin2,pgdmin3,PostgreSQL,postgresql,postgres,sql,database,development,gui,administration,tool,software,free,pg,pg-admin</Keywords>
			<Char_Desc_45>PostgreSQLにとって中心の管理</Char_Desc_45>
			<Char_Desc_80>PostgreSQLデータベースのためのグラフィカルな管理インターフェース</Char_Desc_80>
			<Char_Desc_250>PostgreSQLデータベースにおける中心で自由に管理できます。グラフィカルな管理インターフェース、SQLクエリーツール、手続きのコード・エディター、および多くを含みます。ほとんどのユーザーの要求に答えるようにデザインました。.</Char_Desc_250>
			<Char_Desc_450>PostgreSQLデータベースにおける中心で自由に管理できます。グラフィカルな管理インターフェース、SQLクエリーツール、手続きのコード・エディター、および多くを含みます。シンプルなSQLクエリーを書くことから開発途中の複雑なデータベースへ、pgAdminIIIは、ほとんどのユーザーの要求に答えるようにデザインされています。３０以上の言語で利用できて、およびいくつかのオペレーティングシステムで可能です。.</Char_Desc_450>
			<Char_Desc_2000>PostgreSQLデータベースにおける中心で自由に管理できます。グラフィカルな管理インターフェース、SQLクエリーツール、手続きのコード・エディター、および多くを含みます。シンプルなSQLクエリーを書くことから開発途中の複雑なデータベースへ、pgAdminIIIは、ほとんどのユーザーの要求に答えるようにデザインされています。グラフィカルなインターフェースは、すべてのPostgreSQL特徴をサポートして、管理を簡単にします。３０以上の言語で、MSウィンドウズ、GNU/Linux、およびFreeBSDを含むいくつかのオペレーティングシステムので利用できます。</Char_Desc_2000>
		</Japanese>


		<Taiwanese>
			<Keywords>pgadmin,pgadmin2,pgdmin3,PostgreSQL,postgresql,postgres,sql,database,development,gui,administration,tool,software,free,pg,pg-admin</Keywords>
			<Char_Desc_45>PostgreSQL資料庫管理中心</Char_Desc_45>
			<Char_Desc_80>免費的PostgreSQL資料庫管理中心</Char_Desc_80>
			<Char_Desc_250>免費的PostgreSQL資料庫管理中心，它針對大多數使用者需求而設計，包含了圖形化的管理介面、SQL查詢工具、程序碼編輯器和更多其它的功能。</Char_Desc_250>
			<Char_Desc_450>免費的PostgreSQL資料庫管理中心。包含圖形化的管理介面、SQL查詢工具、程序碼編輯器和更多其它的功能。pgAdmin III是針對大多數使用者需求而設計，功能涵蓋從編寫簡單的SQL查詢到發展複雜的資料庫。目前已被翻譯為超過30種以上的語言，可以執行於多種作業系統。</Char_Desc_450>
			<Char_Desc_2000>免費的PostgreSQL資料庫管理中心。包含圖形化的管理介面、SQL查詢工具、程序碼編輯器和更多其它的功能。pgAdmin III是針對大多數使用者需求而設計，功能涵蓋從編寫簡單的SQL查詢到發展複雜的資料庫。它的圖形化介面支援所有的PostgreSQL特性，使您的管理工作變得更容易。目前已被翻譯為超過30種以上的語言，可以執行於多種作業系統，如微軟的視窗系統、GNU/Linux和FreeBSD。</Char_Desc_2000>
		</Taiwanese>
	</Program_Descriptions>
	<Web_Info>
		<Application_URLs>
			<Application_Info_URL>http://www.pgadmin.org</Application_Info_URL>
			<Application_Order_URL></Application_Order_URL>
			<Application_Screenshot_URL>http://www.pgadmin.org/pgadmin3/shots/pgadmin3_win32.png</Application_Screenshot_URL>
			<Application_Icon_URL>http://www.pgadmin.org/pgadmin3/shots/pgadmin3.png</Application_Icon_URL>
			<Application_XML_File_URL>http://pgadmin.postgresql.org/pgadmin3/cnt/pgadmin3.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
		</Application_URLs>
		<Download_URLs>
			<Primary_Download_URL>ftp://ftp3.us.postgresql.org/pub/postgresql/pgadmin3/release/win32/pgadmin3.zip</Primary_Download_URL>
			<Secondary_Download_URL>ftp://ftp2.de.postgresql.org/pub/comp/os/unix/database/postgresql/pgadmin3/release/win32/pgadmin3.zip</Secondary_Download_URL>
			<Additional_Download_URL_1>ftp://ftp4.ar.postgresql.org/pub/mirrors/postgresql/pgadmin3/release/win32/pgadmin3.zip</Additional_Download_URL_1>
			<Additional_Download_URL_2>ftp://ftp5.tw.postgresql.org/pub/Unix/Database/PostgreSQL/pgadmin3/release/win32/pgadmin3.zip</Additional_Download_URL_2>
		</Download_URLs>
	</Web_Info>
	<Permissions>
		<Distribution_Permissions>
		BY INSTALLING OR DISTRIBUTING PGADMIN AND RELATED SOFTWARE, YOU AGREE WITH
THE FOLLOWING DISCLAIMER:

PGADMIN AND RELATED SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED WITHOUT GUARANTEE OR WARRANTY OF
ANY KIND. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT ALLOWED BY LAW YOU AGREE THAT THE PGADMIN
DEVELOPMENT TEAM MEMBERS, CONTRIBUTERS OR DISTRIBUTORS OF THE SOFTWARE CANNOT
AND WILL NOT BE HELD LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT OR INDIRECT DAMAGE OR LOSSES CAUSED
WHOLLY OR IN PART BY THE SOFTWARE.

IN COUNTRIES WHERE THE ABSENCE OF LIABILITY MAY NOT EXIST OR BE RESTRICTED
BY LAW, PGADMIN DEVELOPMENT TEAM MEMBERS, CONTRIBUTORS AND DISTRIBUTORS
LIABILITY SHALL BE LIMITED TO ONE EURO.

		pgAdmin can be distributed under the terms of the Artistic licence available from http://www.pgadmin.org/pgadmin3/cnt/licence.txt
		</Distribution_Permissions>
		<EULA>
		BY INSTALLING OR DISTRIBUTING PGADMIN AND RELATED SOFTWARE, YOU AGREE WITH THE FOLLOWING DISCLAIMER:

PGADMIN AND RELATED SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED WITHOUT GUARANTEE OR WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT ALLOWED BY LAW YOU AGREE THAT THE PGADMIN DEVELOPMENT TEAM MEMBERS, CONTRIBUTERS OR DISTRIBUTORS OF THE SOFTWARE CANNOT AND WILL NOT BE HELD LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT OR INDIRECT DAMAGE OR LOSSES CAUSED WHOLLY OR IN PART BY THE SOFTWARE.

IN COUNTRIES WHERE THE ABSENCE OF LIABILITY MAY NOT EXIST OR BE RESTRICTED BY LAW, PGADMIN DEVELOPMENT TEAM MEMBERS, CONTRIBUTORS AND DISTRIBUTORS LIABILITY SHALL BE LIMITED TO ONE EURO.

		pgAdmin is a free software project released under the Artistic licence available from http://www.pgadmin.org/pgadmin3/cnt/licence.txt
		</EULA>
	</Permissions>
	<ASP>
		<ASP_Member>N</ASP_Member>
		<ASP_Member_Number/>
	</ASP>
	<PADRING>
		http://www.aquafold.com/PAD_FILE.XML
		http://www.alligatorsql.de/download/alligator.xml
		http://www.casestudio.com/padinfo/casestudio.xml
		http://www.degisy.com/padinfo/dbw5_eng.xml
		http://www.ems-hitech.com/pad/pgmanager_pad.xml
		http://www.fabforce.net/dbdesigner4/various/win.xml
		http://www.microolap.com/pad/pgisql.xml
		http://www.pgadmin.org/pgadmin3/cnt/pgadmin3.xml
		http://www.sqlboss.com/PAD_SQLBoss_Dev_WIN.xml
	</PADRING>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
